One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud.
Always stand up! Raise our unyielding flag.
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward! Hands up!!
"I'm almost there, just a little further and I'll have the answer."
That's what I believed as I sailed into this new world.
That's right, the pieces of our dreams are joined together as one.
We're connected by unwavering bonds, let's head for a bright future!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud.
Always stand up! Raise our unyielding flag.
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Always look up!
Keep your head held high!
Always step up!
Fly over the waves!
Our dreams have been carefully joined together.
Now let's head for the future!
We drift forward, riding the waves,
meeting people and saying goodbye, then doing it again,
all under this flag...
Pain I don't want to forget is kept in my heart.
There was a day when I softly carved it there.
I won't let anyone take my freedom.
I grasp it tightly in my hands!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud.
Always stand up! Raise our unyielding flag.
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Always look up!
Keep your head held high!
Always step up!
Fly over the waves!
Our dreams have been carefully joined together.
Now let's head for the future!
Vice Admiral vs. Vice Admiral and
the Truth Behind Punk Hazard's Destruction!
Building B, 2nd Floor - Examination Room
One of you little brats turned into a dragon?
Ah! I mean, little kids!
Missy, where did you hear about that?
I saw it myself. I was hiding.
It was in the secret room, so I never told anyone.
We came here together on the same boat,
so I'm worried about him.
Oh, I see. But he's fine.
This laboratory is huge.
There's plenty of infirmaries,
so he's just been moved somewhere else.
But is he eating now?
Why wasn't he eating?
No, he's eating. You don't need to worry.
He's fine.
Listen up. You can never talk about him,
or the secret room, to anyone else.
Building C, 4th Floor - Caesar's Office
Hey, bird-lady! What're you doing?!
Ten Layer Igloo!
It's ten igloos nested one inside the other.
I can make them one after another,
so it won't break easily.
So what, you're just wasting time?
In that case, I'll break them all at once!
Stop doing pointless things!
I'm not planning on losing to you!
I'm sure you're not.
I'm also sure that I'm not as strong as you.
But...
the strongest fighter doesn't always win, do they?
Cold...
You're like ice.
Lemme go!
I'm not going to let you go.
Once in my embrace,
you no longer have the strength to resist.
Already, this cold body of mine
has started to drain your vitality.
Look, we're surrounded by this thick snow.
You're irresistibly sleepy, aren't you?
Feels good, doesn't it?
That's right, forget your worries and close your eyes.
Let it all go.
Jet Spear!
The floor?!
What a surprising reserve of hidden strength.
But from here you'll just fall into the ducts
and end up deep underground in the garbage dump.
Unless you can fly, you'll never get back up.
You put yourself into your own grave.
Farewell.
Building B, 3rd Floor - Near Biscuits Room
You must never eat that candy again.
Shut up! Get out of the way!
Don't you want to go home?
I know it's hard, but you have to be strong!
I won't let you past me.
I won't let you into the Biscuits Room!
Candy!
Stop!
Ow! It hurts!
Oh, sorry. I didn't mean to hurt you...
Out of the way, you monster!
The candy is ours!
It's over. I can neither fight nor stop them.
Now's our chance!
Let's go to the Biscuits Room!
You can't! You can't go there!
Oh no! The effect of the Rumble Ball is fading.
We can eat the candy!
Candy!
Go to the Biscuits Room!
We can eat candy!
Hey! Wait!
It's no use. My body won't move, damn it.
Chopper, what's happening?
Momonosuke! Where are you?!
I'm so happy you came for me.
Tell us the situation, Chopper!
Just as we thought, Caesar is turning them into giants to create fearsome soldiers.
It's too much for me to handle by myself.
At any rate, please stop the children, quickly!
The Biscuits Room is down the corridor and on the left.
That's where the candy is.
A girl named Mocha is there, all alone.
She's still sane and has been helping me.
Somehow the two of us
managed to hold everyone back for a while...
but we couldn't stop them.
She's guarding the candy in the Biscuits Room now.
We've made it to the Biscuits Room!
Candy!
Mocha's in danger!
Mille Fleur...
Thousand flowers
Gigantesco Mano!
Gigantic Hand
You're in the way!
Stopping them is not gonna be easy.
If they're gonna be like that, they're forcing our hands.
Mocha, give us the candy!
No, you can't! I can't give this to you!
Candy!
This is bad candy!
Pull yourselves together!
We asked Chopper-chan to save us!
Give it!
No!
If you don't listen to them, we won't be able to go home!
That won't work. Run away! Now, Mocha!
Hey, wait! Hogging it is unfair!
Get her!
Stop! Are you going to keep it all for yourself?!
What?!
The exit's sealed.
It's Monet-san.
Who's that chick?
It's her!
Hey, see?! It's the bird-lady I told you about!
Mocha, you shouldn't be selfish.
Split it up and share with everyone.
Building D - SAD Manufacturing Room
Room!
Heart, return!
Counter Shock!
I have a message from Joker.
He says that it's a shame.
It didn't work?
Snatching my heart back from Caesar would have gone according to plan.
The only thing I didn't expect was your arrival,
Vergo.
It's san!
I'm rather busy at the moment, but I guess you won't wait...
Vice-Admiral Smoker.
I was planning to silence you either way.
Get it over with, then. I don't think I can stand looking at this trash before me for much longer...
Pirate Vergo.
What is this dangerous looking room?
It's something you don't need to know about.
Vergo, I don't want my subordinates to find out about this.
They love you like a father.
To find out that you're Joker's dog...
Oh, it's too late to do anything about that.
I already met them a few minutes ago.
What did you do?
What indeed?
Vergo!
You seem pretty upset, Smoker-kun.
Are you seriously worried about those misfit Marines?
As base leader I can do whatever I want to my useless subordinates.
And since you guys know too much, I'm gonna have to make you disappear.
It doesn't matter how long you've been with them,
or that you're their base leader.
Since you left the base, they've become my subordinates.
Don't you lay a finger on them!
Building B, G-5 Group
What happened here?
Hot, hot it's damn hot!
There's nowhere left to walk.
Just what on earth happened here?!
Hurry it up, bring the injured people to the front.
And protect Tashigi-chan!
Please stop acting so friendly! We're enemies!
That's only according to society's rules, pirates are free to do what they want.
The way you kicked that fake Vergo is enough to even make a man fall in love with you.
That was really cool, bro.
Shut it! I said I don't want any cheers from the men!
Please stop calling that pirate "bro"!
A tank exploded!
This is bad. It punched a hole through the wall.
On the other side too. Damn it all!
Run, you guys!
The gas is leaking in from outside!
It's the killer gas from earlier!
If you don't want to die then start running!
Even this huge space in Building B will be flooded with gas in no time!
Stop whining and get moving!
Tashigi-chan, run!
You'll die if you hesitate! Just focus on going the right way!
Black Leg!
Hurry up, you guys! You're gonna die at that pace!
Building R, 2nd Floor - The Secret Room
Those guys are such idiots.
Who would've thought that they'd let in the Shinokuni themselves?
But if they die where they are, it won't be on my experiment broadcast.
Hey, close the gates to Buildings C and D.
Okay, but what about Building R?
Leave that one open.
I'm gonna set a trap for those idiots on the first floor of Building R.
They are heading for Gate 66 in the R-Building.
I'll lead them there to make sure that they don't get sidetracked.
I really hate this room.
The second floor of the Building R - The Secret Room.
I never wanted to use this room.
But I can't let the Straw Hats get away.
They've gotten far too confident.
I have Joker backing me.
Once they're in that room, I'll kill them all.
Master, we finished our preparations for battle a long time ago.
Why did you call us here to the old office of that despicable Vegapunk?
Vegapunk created that incident four years ago, so he is our enemy as well.
Are you sure we should be sitting here doing nothing?
Shouldn't we go and fight them?
Nope, it's fine.
You guys are my special forces,
I don't wish for your blood to be spilled in vain.
M-Master!
Now then, it's time to explain my plan.
I've closed the doors leading to Buildings C and D.
so now all open corridors in the laboratory lead to the room below us,
the first floor of the Building R.
The Straw Hats, G-5 and the children...
All the survivors will end up in this room.
And the first floor of Building R has air vents.
Of course, those air vents will flood it with Shinokuni.
There will be nowhere for them to run.
That way, no one can survive.
With all the gates closed, it will become one big gas chamber.
The video feed from that room is already being sent to all the brokers in the New World.
That way I can show my skill to the entire underworld.
If I may, Master Caesar...
Were you the one that created that horrifying poison gas?
But it looks like the poisonous gas that Dr. Vegapunk released four years ago.
It really creeps us all out.
This is...
a scientific battle for vengeance!
Listen, my subordinates...
On that day, I tried to stop him.
The mad scientist Vegapunk.
"If you lost control of that weapon,
just what do you think would happen to all the people on this island? Stop it, Vegapunk!"
But still, the accident occurred.
And he continues to lead the Navy's top scientists,
as the world's greatest scientist!
I can't stand it!
Can we really allow the cruel man who hurt all of you...
to keep being praised as the greatest scientist in the world?!
Master!
That's why I have have to prove that I'm better than him!
By creating a weapon of mass destruction even though I didn't want to!
To prove that I am the world's greatest scientist, not him!
When the Navy accepts that, and I'm the science division's lead scientist,
then my dream to use science to bring about world peace can come true!
Master!
I'm sorry Master. We're ashamed to have ever doubted you.
You really are our god of salvation!
Stop it, Caesar!
Stop the experiment right now!
If you lost control of that weapon,
just what do you think would happen to all the people on this island?
Silence, you brainless fools!
Where do you think we are?!
It's the Navy's research facility.
They want us to create a weapon that could kill many pirates at once.
They don't want a weapon that would kill innocent civilians as well!
You idiot.
That's what we call acceptable losses.
It's their own fault for being in the line of fire.
If we destroy everything, the world will truly be at peace.
You are so...
Cruel?
Now, isn't that funny!
How is this any different from you experimenting on the prisoners here, like they were garbage?
The current Fleet Admiral Sengoku is naive,
but Admiral Akainu should see the value of my weapon.
Now if you understand, get out of here.
You're in the way!
Vegapunk is just jealous of my genius.
I heard that he failed at gigantification again.
This is science, not magic! Humans aren't going to grow into giants without effort!
I told him to kidnap a bunch of growing kids and shove different drugs down their throats.
Wh-
W-What are you doing?!
Stay quiet and come with us.
Vegapunk, what is the meaning of this?!
You have been expelled from the science division.
Your research is far too dangerous.
I can no longer overlook it.
Don't you screw with me!
Stop it, Caesar!
The passageway between Buildings C and B has been sealed.
The passageway between Buildings B and D has been sealed.
It is now impossible to enter Buildings C or D from the Building B.
Run like your lives depend on it!
Building C - Garbage Dump
You just spoke now, didn't you?
What are you?
I...
I would ask that you identify yourself first!